It is now the morning chime. My name is Ayaka Yasumoto, attendance number 5 at the Municipal Ebiichi Junior High School. It has begun.
It's time for the Stada Gamers Club. This time, everyday new color real horror.
We will be playing the first episode of Tsugu no Hi. In the last delivery.
I wasn't scared at all, but a little bit, because today is a Japanese one.
I'm a little nervous, but
I'd like to begin!
Here they come!
I'm going to walk.
Does this mean I'm walking with this boy?
What's that?
Oh, he's trying to rattle us with sound.
Look, there's something here.
I just saw something.
What's that?
It just disappeared.
Is this the opening?
I thought it had already started.
Is it starting?
It's started.
Watch out!
Watch out. It was just a strike.
Is it the wind? This is a little bad.
This, this...
It's a little bit like this arrow cracking.
Here we go again.
He's trying to scare me, you know.
Oh, there he is. See, this is the type.
Here they come.
Let's get some.
There he is. There he is. There he is.
I saw him, but he said, "meow.
I said, "meow!
There it is! There it is!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is this how the game is supposed to be played?
Is this a game where we follow the same path?
Is that what you're saying?
My head hurts today.
Unlike the girls.
In the mirror and then behind me.
Sound. Aah! Huh!
Here it comes. It's a ghost that scares you in a Japanese way. The one with the white face.
Huh? I wonder if it's that thing that was there earlier.
Oh, that's what you mean.
Oh, so that's what it's about... the time for stories... the Entertainer's Nation... and now we're back to this routine again.
Let's move on.
My shoulders are getting heavy, which means he's already got me.
That guy.
He's got my shoulder.
He's got my shoulder!
It's like he's trying to scare us, you know? Huh? Huh! He wasn't here earlier.
Huh!
Look at me!
Oh, there he is!
You just surprised me.
I know I sounded surprised.
You sound surprised today.
You're right.
I'm going to scream today.
Wow, that's a lot of progress.
Is that what's going on?
Oh, my God, the place has changed.
He doesn't have a headache or anything like that on his face anymore.
This guy's getting to me.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
What's going on, what's going on, what's going on, what's going on, what's going on?
It's getting bigger.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here...
What's going to happen to her?
What's going to happen to him?
What?
Huh?
What? Oh, you know, that place... where the end rolls are always at the end of the show? It's going away!
Mommy!
Yes, ma'am.
Hmm? Not yet.
I'm a...
Yes!
I'm...
I'm Sian!
So...
Next day, Episode 1
I finished the gameplay.
I finished.
Actually, when the staff saw me not cackling at all during the last horror game delivery, they said, "That's not what we're looking for.
Fans, the people watching, you know. So I was told to say "Caw" no matter how surprised I was.
But I didn't know where to say "caw.
Maybe I'll find out when I get here.
After a little while after they came.
Oh, well, normal people say "caw" here.
Rather, the two guys in front of me, who are a little bit scared
They shrug their shoulders like this every time.
It's like, "Oh, I didn't know it was this or that.
So I don't have to intentionally surprise them.
I'm really happy, aren't I?
That's it for the Stardust Gamers Club.
Thank you all for watching.
See you soon!
Next time I'll be scared!